YOUTUBE GOLD AWARD
YOU JOINED US
WHEN THE LAME WALKED
WHEN THE BLIND SAW
YOU JOINED US
WHEN THE DEAF HEARD
WHEN THE SITUATION SAID NO
BUT JESUS SAID YES
YOU JOINED US TO REACH OUT
TO A TROUBLED WORLD
AND BECAUSE OF YOU,
EMMANUEL TV HAS REACHED OVER
1 MILLION SUBSCRIBERS ON YOUTUBE
THIS AWARD IS FOR YOU
THIS IS YOUR LETTER
FROM YOUTUBE
Let us now read the content of the letter from YouTube.
You're bigger than Vancouver.
You're bigger than Venice.
You're even bigger than Las Vegas.
One million subscribers.
Maybe you've imagined that day for a long time,
or maybe you never thought you'd grow so big.
Either way, not much can match the satisfaction of finding out that your creativity,
that your ideas, that your voice speaks to one million people across the globe.
We know that being able to touch the lives of so many people is reward enough.
But we're incredibly proud of all you've done,
so we hope you'll accept this Gold Creator Award as a token of our esteem.
With your track record, we suspect you're only going to keep growing.
And we can't wait to see you reach the next milestone: 10 million subscribers.
It may seem far away, but remember the days when you were psyched to have a thousand?
You've amazed us.
Keep daring, keep dreaming big... and keep creating!
You're the inspiration for everything we do.
Sincerely, Susan Wojcicki
CEO, YouTube
CONTINUE TO JOIN US AS TOGETHER,
WE CHANGE LIVES, NATIONS AND THE WORLD
THROUGH CHRIST
IN THE POWER OF THE HOLY SPIRIT.
TT: Mel Flowers 07/01/2019